Guide to the Institute for Research on Educational Finance and Governance (U.S.) Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 84-B2. Jensen. Reading, 'Riting and Rights: Busing for Racial Balance (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 84-B3. Tsang and Levin. The Economics of Over-education (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 84-B4. Willms. Public and Private School Outcomes: Results From High School and Beyond Follow- up Study (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 84-B5. Catterall and Brizantine. Prop 13: Effects of High School Curriculum 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 84-B6. Grubb. The Bandwagon Once More: Vocational Preparation for High Tech Occupations (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 84-B7. Kirst, Meister and Rowley. Policy Issue Networks: Their Influence On State Policymaking (Box 10, Folder 10)
- 84-B8. Hartog. Individual Schooling Decisions and Labor Market Allocations: Vertical and Horizontal (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 84-B9. Levin and Tsang. The Economics of Student Time (Box 10, Folder 12)
- 84-B10. Tsang. The Impact of Over-education on Productivity: A Case Study of Skill (Box 10, Folder 13)
- 84-B11. Strober-Lanford. The Percentage of Women in Public School Teaching: 1850- 1880 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- 84-C1. Levin. State Planning For Higher Education Jobs in Age of High Technology (Box 10, Folder 15)
- 84-C2. Hess and Miura. Issues in Training Teachers to Use Microcomputers (Box 10, Folder 16)
- 84-C3. Valencia. School Closures and Policy Issues (Box 10, Folder 17)
- P/NP 1/Crain: Private Schools and Black and White Segregation (Box 10, Folder 18)
- P/NP 2/Lines: Treatment of Religion in Public Schools and the Impact on Private Education (Box 10, Folder 19)
- P/NP 3/James: The Public and Private Divide of Responsibility for Education: An International Comparison (Box 10, Folder 20)
- P/NP 4/ Darling-Hammond/Nataraj-Kirby: Public Policy and Private Choice: Minnesota (Box 10, Folder 21)
- P/NP 5/Willms: Patterns of Academic Achievement in Public and Private Schools (Box 10, Folder 22)
- P/NP 6/ Alexander: Comparing Public and Private School Effect: Evidence and Issues (Box 11, Folder 1)
- P/NP 7/ Catterall: Private School Participation and Public Policy (Box 11, Folder 2)
- P/NP 8/ Haertel: Comparing Achievement in Public and Private Schools (Box 11, Folder 3)
- P/NP 9/ Hoffer, Greely, Coleman: Catholic High School Effects on Achievement Growth (Box 11, Folder 4)
- P/NP 10/ Talbert: Sector Organizing Condition Implicit For School Effectiveness (Box 11, Folder 5)
- P/NP 11/ Alexander and Pallas: School Sector and Cognitive Performance: When is a Little a Little? (Box 11, Folder 6)
- P/NP 12/ Cooper: The Changing Universe of U.S. Private Schools (Box 11, Folder 7)
- P/NP 12/ Cooper: The Changing Universe of U.S. Private Schools (Box 11, Folder 8)
- TTC-1. Jensen. TTC: Constitutional and Legal Implications (Box 11, Folder 9)
- TTC-3. Murnane. Understanding Public and Private Schools: The Importance of Student Body Composition, Sorting and Regulations (Box 11, Folder 10)
- TTC-4. Sherman. Public Finance of Private Schools: Observations from Abroad (Box 11, Folder 11)
- TTC-5. Osman and Gemello. Analysis of the Choice For Public and Private Education (Box 11, Folder 12)
- TTC-6. James. Public versus Nonpublic Education in Historical Perspective (Box 11, Folder 13)
- TTC-7. Glazer. The Future Under Tuition Tax Credits (Box 11, Folder 14)
- TTC-8. Muller. The Social and Political Consequences of Increased Public Support (Box 11, Folder 15)
- TTC-9. Willms. Achievement Outcomes in Public and Private Schools: A Closer Look (Box 11, Folder 16)
- TTC-10. Longanecer. Public Cost of Tuition Tax Credit (Box 11, Folder 17)
- TTC-11. Levin. Educational Choice and the Pains of Democracy (Box 11, Folder 18)
- TTC-12. Encarnation. Public Finance and Regulation of Non-Public Education (Box 11, Folder 19)
- TTC-13. Catterall. Tuition Tax Credits: Issues of Equity (Box 11, Folder 20)
- TTC-14. Erickson. Private Schools in Contemporary Perspective (Box 11, Folder 21)
- TTC-15. Sullivan. Comparing Efficiency Between Public and Private Schools (Box 12, Folder 1)
- TTC-16. Jenson. TTCs: Has the Supreme Court Cleared the Way? (Box 12, Folder 2)
- 85-A1. An Index of Publications For Years 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- 85-A2. Levin. Solving the Shortage of Math and Science Teachers (Box 12, Folder 4)
- 85-A3. Creighton and Strang. Studying the Organizational Structure of Public Education (Box 12, Folder 5)
- 85-A4. Rumberger. The Impact of Education on Productivity and Earnings (Box 12, Folder 6)
- 85-A5. McLaughlin, Pfeiffer, Owens and Yee. State Policy and Teaching Excellence (Box 12, Folder 7)
- 85-A6. McLaughlin et al. State and Local Response to Chapter 1 of the Education Consolidation and Improvement Act, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 85-A7. Responding to the Constancy of Change: New Technologies and Future Demands on U.S. Education. (Box 12, Folder 9)
- 85-A8. Carnoy. The labor Marker in Silicon Valley and Its Implications for Education (Box 12, Folder 10)
- 85-A9. Elmore. Reforming the Finance And Structure of Education and Training (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 85-A10. Jensen. Judicial Activism and Special Education (Box 12, Folder 12)
- 85-A11. Meyer, Scott, Strang and Creighton. Bureaucratization without Centralization: Changes in the Organizational System of American Public Education, 1940-1980. (Box 12, Folder 13)
- 85-A12. Cohen and Murnane. The Merits of Merit Pay (Box 12, Folder 14)
- 85-A13. Levin and Meister. Educational Technology and Computers: Promises, Promises, Always Promises (Box 12, Folder 15)
- 85-A14. Murnane and Cohen. Merit Pay and The Evaluation Problem: Understanding Why Most Merit Plans Fail and Few Survive (Box 12, Folder 16)
- 85-A15. Chubb and Moe. Politics, Markets and the Organization of Schools (Box 12, Folder 17)
- 85-A16. Jensen. State Courts and the New Federalism (Box 12, Folder 18)
- 85-B1. Levin. The Educationally Disadvantages: A National Crisis (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 85-B2. Muta. Education and Training in Japan in the Cybernetic Age (Box 13, Folder 2)
- 85-B3. Bosch-Font. Retail Banking and Technology: An Analysis of Skill Mix Transformation (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 85-B4. Sotoo and Ito. Influence on Micro Electronics on Employment in Japan (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 85-B5. Sotoo and Ito. Influence on Micro Electronics on Employment in Japan (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 85-C1. Rumberger. The Growing Problem of Youth Unemployment: Causes and Policy Solutions (Box 13, Folder 6)
- 85-C2. Jensen. Court Reform of Public Institutions: What Determines Impact? (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 85-C3. Kirst. Sustaining State Education Reform Momentum (Box 13, Folder 8)